Hi, welcome to learn and master guitar,
嗨，欢迎来到 learn and master guitar ，
on this session, we're gonna talk about chords,
在这节课上，我们将谈论和弦，
we're going to learn about what chords are the basic chords,
我们将学习什么是基本和弦，
what chords are open chords and bar chords
什么和弦是开放和弦和横按和弦，
and the chords that every guitarist who calls himself a guitarist needs to know certain chords
以及每个自称吉他手的吉他手都需要知道的和弦，
and that's we're going to talk about today,
这就是我们今天要谈论的，
the intro to all of that,
所有这些的介绍，
we can do some songs involving chords,
我们弹一些涉及和弦的歌曲，
in our guitar tips section,
在吉他技巧部分，
we're going to talk about sounding your best when playing chords,
我们将讨论在演奏和弦时发出最好的声音，
a little bit about strumming that sort of thing.
关于扫弦这类事情。
So I'll see you there.
我们在那里见。
Okay, now the first thing you want to think of when you're doing chords is
好的，现在你想要做和弦的第一件事是
going to make sure review our hand position,
确保复习我们手的位置，
we talked about hand position at the very beginning,
我们一开始就谈到了手的位置，
let's kind of review,
让我们复习一下，
what a good hand position should be.
一个好的手的位置应该是什么。
For we've got a good pick position right here,
因为我们在这里有一个很好的拨片位置，
we're holding our pick nice and strong,
我们很好有力地持有拨片，
we don't want to hold it too loose,
我们不想把它握得太松，
if we hold it too loose,
如果我们把它握得太松，
it just doesn't work well with chords,
它就不能跟和弦很好地工作，
so we want to hold up, hold a pick with a little bit of strength in it.
所以我们想持有拨片，带有一点力量。
Okay, on our left hand,
好的，在我们的左手，
we want to make sure that when we're playing these chords,
我们要确保当我们演奏这些和弦的时候，
that our hand is in a good balanced position,
我们的手处于一个很好的平衡位置，
our wrist is down,
我们的手腕向下，
we've got a little bit of air space here,
我们这里有一点空间，
I'm gonna have my thumb and my wrist way up like this,
我会像这样把我的拇指和手腕向上，
we'll come all the way down like this,
我们会像这样下去，
bring that wrist out,
把手腕拿出来，
now you don't need to brace when you're doing chords,
现在你做和弦的时候不需要支撑，
we've talked about brace soon,
我们很快就谈到了支撑，
that was good, we're doing single notes
这很好，我们在做单音符，
and we had to figure out which string we need to play,
我们必须弄清楚我们需要演奏哪一根弦，
it doesn't work that way with chords,
和弦不是这样的，
chords go ahead and [] your fingers underneath your hand
和弦继续，你的手指在你的手掌下面，
and we'll just do it,
我们就这么做，
without bracing,
没有支撑，
that's what we need to do when we get into strumming.
这是我们开始扫弦时需要做的。
Okay, the chords, we're going to be talking about are open chords,
好的，我们将谈论的和弦是开放和弦，
what open chords are,
开放和弦是什么，
open is telling you that there is an open string involved in the chord,
开放是告诉你和弦中有空弦，
okay, later on, we're going to talk about bar chords,
好的，稍后，我们将讨论横按和弦，
which are chords that do not have any open strings on them
也就是没有任何空弦的和弦，
and that use one finger to cover more than one string,
用一根手指覆盖不止一根弦，
that's a bar,
这就是横按，
these first few that we're going to cover are open chords
我们将覆盖的前几个和弦是开放和弦，
and that's the ones we're going to focus on right now,
这是我们现在要关注的，
so let's talk about the first set of chords.
所以我们来谈谈第一组和弦。
Now, in this session, we're going to learn three different sets of chords,
现在，在这节课中，我们将学习三组不同的和弦，
I group them together,
我把它们组合在一起，
because really a finger combinations that work well with each other,
因为它们的手指组合彼此配合得很好，
so you'll notice some are C, some are D, some are Es,
所以你会注意到一些是 C ，一些是 D ，一些是 E ，
they kind of go in between different ones,
它们在不同的之间，
and it may be a little confusing to keep up with the names,
记下名字可能有点困惑，
but I did it to introduce the ones that would be the easiest first,
但我这样做是为了首先介绍最容易的那些，
so here's the first batch of chords that we're going to cover.
所以这是我们现在要涵盖的第一批和弦。
Now, actually I've already kind of snuck in the first four that we need to do,
实际上我已经偷偷地插入了我们需要做的前四个和弦，
way back in session two I believe it was,
回到第二节课，
we covered a C chord,
我们讲了 C 和弦，
let's review what a C chord is,
让我们回顾一下 C 和弦是什么，
the six string, we don't have anything on it,
第六弦，我们没有任何东西，
there's an x over that chord block,
在和弦区块上有一个 x ，
fifth string, I've got my third finger,
第五弦，我使用无名指，
fourth string, I've got my second finger,
第四弦，我使用中指，
third string is open,
第三弦是开放的，
first finger is C, on that second string,
食指是 C ，在第二弦上，
and the last string is open,
最后一根弦是开放的，
let's play altogether,
让我们一起演奏，
each note individually,
每个音符单独演奏，
make sure they're all sounding clean
确保它们听起来都是干净的，
and sounding out nice and strong,
听起来又好又有力，
no buzz,
没有嗡嗡声，
one more time,
再来一次，
now together.
现在一起。
Now, sometimes it may be hard for you to grab a couple of these chords,
现在，有时候你可能很难抓住几个这样的和弦，
if you want to kind of the easy way to do some of these chords
如果你想要简单地做这些和弦，
is just to take the bottom half of the chord,
就是把按住和弦的下半部分，
in this one,
在这个（和弦）里面，
it would just be the E, the C and G, the lowest three strings
它将是 E C G ，最低的三根弦，
and just play those to get you started,
只需要弹奏它们就可以开始了，
but ideally we want to eventually be able to stretch our hands wide enough
但是理想情况下，我们希望最终能够把手伸得足够大，
to get that E and C in there,
以得到 E 和 C ，
doing a full C chord.
做一个完整的 C 和弦。
Okay, the next chord we learned was a G7,
好的，下一个我们学到的和弦是 G7 ，
we move our fingers up one string set here
我们将手指向上移动一根弦，
and down to the first string there,
然后向下移动到第一弦，
so I've got my third finger, my second finger,
这样我就有了无名指，中指，
open string, open string, open string,
空弦，空弦，空弦，
and then my first finger on that first string.
然后我的食指在第一弦上。
Okay, let's go note for note,
好的，让我们一个音符一个音符地弹，
one more time,
再来一次，
now altogether,
现在，一起，
that's a G7 chord.
这是 G7 和弦。
Now, if we put them both together,
现在如果我们把它们放在一起，
we've got a C, we've got a G7.
我们有 C ，我们有 G7 。
In the last session, we learned about Am,
在上一节课中，我们学习了 Am ，
which is a five string chord,
它是一个五弦和弦，
we don't play that sixth string,
我们不演奏第六弦，
it's got an x above it,
它上面有一个 x ，
we have an open A,
我们有空弦 A ，
second finger on this E,
中指在这个 E 上，
third finger squeezing up underneath this, on the A,
无名指挤在这里，在 A 上面，
first finger on the C,
食指在 C 上，
and an open E there,
然后一个空弦 E ，
that's A minor, abbreviation for Am,
这是 A 小调，缩写为 Am ，
okay, five string chord,
好的，五根弦的和弦，
let's go through just individual notes,
让我们来分别弹每一个音符，
now, altogether.
现在，一起。
Now, E chord is the same chord form,
现在， E 和弦是相同的和弦形式，
we just move everybody up a string set,
我们只是将每个手指向上移动一个弦，
and it's all use all six strings on an E chord,
E 和弦使用所有六根弦，
individual notes,
每个音符，
all together.
所有一起。
Now, the one new chord that we need to touch on
现在我们需要触及的一个新和弦，
is a D minor chord, abbreviated Dm,
是 D 小调和弦，缩写为 Dm ，
this is our first four string chord, that we've come across,
这是我们遇到的第一个四根弦和弦，
doesn't use all six strings or five strings,
没有使用所有的六根弦或五根弦，
this uses just four,
这个只使用四根（弦），
the first two strings have an x [],
前两根弦有 x ，
so don't play those,
所以不要演奏它们，
then we have an open D,
然后我们有空弦 D ，
second finger on the A,
中指在 A 上面，
third finger on that D,
无名指在 D 上面，
first finger on this F,
食指在这个 F 上面，
maybe a little awkward,
可能会有点尴尬，
getting that third finger out there to that D,
把无名指伸向那个 D ，
if you want to, you could squeeze in your pinky there,
你可以把你的小指挤在那里，
but you might get used to playing it the wrong way,
但你可能会习惯用错误的方式演奏，
so I would really recommend that,
所以我真的推荐，
you try and stretch that third finger out to catch that,
你试着伸出无名指来按住它，
all together,
所有一起，
be real careful to only play four strings,
要非常小心地只演奏四根弦，
it's going to get more and more important, which strings which,
哪些弦将变得越来越重要，
if I add those extra two strings in,
如果我加上额外的两根弦，
I get these rumbling down there,
我会听到下面的隆隆声，
which a lot of guitar players do
很多吉他演奏者都会这样做，
and it's real sloppy,
这听起来真的很马虎，
doesn't sound too good,
听起来不太好，
so make sure we know which chords are five string, C and Am,
所以确认哪些弦是五根弦， C Am ，
which chords are six string, G7 and E,
哪些弦是六根弦， G7 和 E ，
and which chords are four string, with that Dm.
哪些和弦是四根弦， Dm 。
Let's start looking at these basic open chord exercises,
让我们开始看这些基本的开放和弦练习，
number one let's look at the first exercise,
第一个，我们来看第一个练习，
we're going to go through four Cs,
我们将弹四个 C ，
then it's four beats of rest,
然后是四个休止符，
four G7s, four beats of rest,
四个 G7 ，四个休止符，
should be no problem for you.
对你来说应该不是问题。
Ready, play,
准备，弹奏，
and four beats of rest, two three,
四拍的休息，2 3 ，
G7.
G7 。
Very good, number two we go between Am and E,
很好，第二个，我们在 Am 和 E 之间，
Am, ready, play,
Am ，准备，弹奏，
E, everybody moves up a string set,
E ，每个手指向上移动一弦，
ready, play.
准备，弹奏。
Very good, okay, now in the third one,
非常好，现在在第三个中，
you'll notice we have eighth notes,
你会注意到我们有八分音符，
well how do we do eighth notes when we're strumming
当我们扫弦的时候，我们怎么弹八分音符，
or how do eighth notes with chords,
或者在和弦中如何弹八分音符，
it involves strumming,
它涉及到扫弦，
let's talk about that for a second.
我们来讨论一下。
On my right hand over here,
在我的右手边，
as I'm coming into play this C,
当我开始演奏这个 C ，
I come down and I hit my fifth string,
我下来，拨动第五弦，
if you can think of,
如果你能想到的话，
it's kind of making a little arc as I'm coming around,
当我转过来的时候，它就像是一个小弧线，
now, if you were a kid,
如果你是个孩子的话，
and somebody gave you a guitar,
有人给了你一把吉他，
chances are you'd probably walk up to it go,
你可能这样弹，
everybody does,
每个人都这样做，
now that motion is actually,
这个动作实际上是，
pretty close to what you need to be doing,
非常接近你需要做的，
you need to just grip grip a pick in it a little bit stronger,
你只需要更有力地握住拨片，
but you want your wrist to be loosed to be loose,
但你想要手腕松开，
it's almost like you're flicking something off of your hand,
就像你从手中弹出什么东西，
that's the that's the motion with your wrist,
这就是你手腕的运动，
if you get it too tight,
如果你把它拉得太紧，
it sounds real choppy
听起来真的很起伏，
and it's not the direction we want to go,
这不是我们想要的方向，
now make sure that your wrist is loose,
确保你的手腕是松的，
you're gripping the pick strong,
你握拨片很紧，
but your wrist is still loose.
但手腕仍然是松弛的。
Let's take a look at three,
让我们来看看第三个，
if I was doing that C,
如果我这样弹 C ，
down and up, we have to do it nice and steady.
下上，我们必须做得又好又稳。
Now I come down with my arc
现在我带着弧线向下，
and when I come back,
当我回来的时候，
I really only hit a couple of them,
我只拨动了其中的几个，
you don't try to be accurate on it,
你不会试图准确地拨动它们，
way back then and then suddenly pull out at the last minute,
往回，然后在最后一刻突然拉出来，
it doesn't work that way,
它不是这样工作的，
just kind of angle the arc of your arm here to go,
只是有点角度，你手臂的弧度在这里，
accurate going down,
准确地向下，
and then you hit some of them coming up,
然后你拨动其中的一些，
accurate going down, some of them coming up.
准确地向下，[其中的一些]向上。
Okay, number three, let's do that one,
好的，第三个，让我们来弹这个，
starts on a C,
从 C 开始，
ready, go,
准备，开始，
down up, down up, down up, down up,
下上下上下上下上，
rest, find that Am,
休息，找到 Am ，
ready, play,
准备，弹奏，
five string chord again,
再说一次五根弦，
try that one again,
再试一次，
go back to that C, two,
回到 C ， 2 ，
ready and C play,
准备， C 弹奏，
slow and even strums,
缓慢平稳地扫弦，
Am, find it,
Am ，找到它，
ready, go, now.
准备，开始，现在。
Good, now let's skip down to number five,
很好，现在让我们跳到第五个，
that gets our Dm chord
有我们的 Dm 和弦，
and then we're gonna go to G7.
然后我们将跳到 G7 。
We're slowly combining these different rhythms,
我们慢慢地结合这些不同的节奏，
first, we just did quarter notes,
首先，我们只做四分音符，
then we did eight notes,
然后我们做八个音符，
now we're going to quarter notes and eighth notes mixed together,
现在我们把四分音符和八分音符混合在一起，
ready, number five, go,
准备，第五个，开始，
rest, get ready for that G7,
休息，为 G7 做好准备，
ready G7.
准备， G7 。
Do it again, Dm ready, go,
再来一次， Dm ，准备，开始，
G7, two, ready, go.
G7 ， 2 ，准备，开始。
Good, now let's learn our second batch of chords.
好的，现在让我们学习第二批和弦。
Okay, for the second batch of chords,
好的，对于第二批和弦，
we're gonna cover the G, D7, Em, and the ever elusive B7,
我们将介绍 G D7 Em 和难理解的 B7 ，
Okay, so we start out with a G,
好的，我们从 G 开始，
now if you look at your chord diagram,
现在如果你看和弦图，
there's actually two different ways that you can finger this one.
有两种不同的方法可以按出这个。
Okay, the more common way is you put your third finger up here on the sixth string,
好的，更常见的方法是你把你的无名指放在第六弦上，
second finger on the fifth string,
中指放在第五弦上，
then you have open string, open string, open string,
然后你有空弦，空弦，空弦，
and then way down at the bottom,
然后在最下面，
you've got your pinky on that high G,
你有小指在高音 G 上，
on that E string, on that first string.
在 E 弦上，在第一弦上。
Now, the other way of fingering it is
现在，另一种指法是，
just switch your fingers around,
交换你的手指，
I have my second finger on that G,
我把中指放在 G 上，
first finger on the B,
食指放在 B 上，
then, open, open, open,
然后，空弦，空弦，空弦，
third finger on that G there.
无名指在 G 上面。
So, either way is right,
所以，无论哪种方式都是正确的，
so you need to find which way is more comfortable for you to play
你需要找出哪种方式对你演奏更舒服，
and it may be in different musical situations,
可能在不同的音乐情况下，
one may be more preferable than the other,
其中一种可能比另一种更合适，
the next chord is a D7,
下一个和弦是 D7 ，
back to those D chord,
回到 D 和弦，
so that means it's a four string chord,
所以这意味着这是一个四根弦的和弦，
I don't play these lower two strings,
我不会演奏下面的两根弦，
so we have an open D,
所以我们有空弦 D ，
second finger on that A,
中指在 A 上，
first finger on that C,
食指在 C 上，
third finger on this #F on the first string.
无名指在 F# ，第一弦上。
Try one more time,
再试一次，
now altogether.
现在一起。
That's a D7,
这是 D7 ，
may be a little tricky getting that third finger underneath there,
把无名指放在下面可能有点棘手，
you just kind of try,
你只要试一试，
it takes a while,
这需要一段时间，
if your chords are initially buzzy
如果你的和弦一开始嗡嗡作响，
and you think, gosh, I'm never gonna get,
你会想，天哪，我永远不会得到它，
it just sounds, it sounds like,
它听起来像是这样，
I'm not getting it,
我得不到它，
it takes a while, I've found,
我发现，这需要一段时间，
in teaching people chords,
在教人们和弦的过程中，
it takes a while for them to get it,
他们需要一段时间才能学会，
some folks get it right off
有些人会马上学会，
and it's not a problem of hand strength or anything like that for them,
对他们来说，手的力量或其他不是问题，
they just get it,
他们就做到了，
other folks they have to strengthen up their hands,
其他人他们必须加强手的力量，
their problem is they're not able to push the strings down hard enough to get that,
他们的问题是，他们不能足够用力地推动琴弦，
other folks they just can't find the sweet spot to it,
其他人，他们只是找不到最合适的位置，
the chords aren't buzzy,
和弦不是嗡嗡作响，
but it's just I got other fingers that are touching the strings all around them
只是我的其他手指在触碰周围的琴弦，
and I end up with these muted sounds,
最后我发出了这些低沉的声音，
so that's why it's important to go one right after the other,
所以这就是为什么一个接一个地演奏是很重要的，
and you may think gosh it just sounds like this
你可能会想，天哪，这听起来就像这样，
and it's not gonna get any better,
它不会变得更好，
but I have not found that to be true,
但我没有发现这是真的，
I've worked with folks with all kinds of different hands, all kinds of different fingers,
我和那些各种不同手、各种不同手指的人合作过，
in in hand strength issues
手的力量问题，
and I have found that in general,
我发现一般来说，
they're able to get it with a little bit of practice,
他们可以通过一点练习来获得它，
it takes a while to find the sweet spot of where to put your fingers
需要一段时间找到你的手指的最佳位置，
to get it all to sound right,
让它听起来正确，
but keep working at it,
但继续努力，
it may not come in a few days,
它可能不会在几天内到来，
maybe a week or two,
也许一到两周，
before you actually get them to open up,
在你真正让它们打开之前，
but once you get them to open up,
但一旦你让它们打开，
they'll be there,
它们就会在那里，
the next one is an Em.
下一个是 Em 。
E chord, all six strings,
E 和弦，所有六根弦，
this one is pretty easy,
这个很简单，
we have open E,
我们有空弦 E ，
second finger on that B,
中指在 B 上面，
third finger on that E,
无名指在 E 上面，
then the rest of them open,
然后其余的空弦，
that's an Em.
这是 Em 。
Now, B7 is the last one in this batch,
现在 B7 是这一批中的最后一个，
second finger on the fifth string,
中指在第五弦上，
five string chord, don't play that sixth string,
五根弦的和弦，不要弹第六根弦，
first finger on that #D,
食指在 D# 上面，
third finger on that A,
无名指在 A 上面，
open B,
空弦 B ，
and pinky on that #F,
小拇指在 F# 上面，
now this one may take a little practice
这个可能需要一些练习，
of getting them all to sound out clearly,
让所有弦声音清晰，
a lot of times, you'll find that that #D won't come out real good,
很多时候，你会发现 D# 的声音不是很好，
because this finger, your second finger,
因为这根手指，你的中指，
he's got his little [], sitting on the string underneath him
它有点[]，靠在下面的弦上，
and it doesn't, it doesn't let him play.
不让它弹奏。
There's really only two problems, why note doesn't sound,
只有两个问题，为什么音符听起来不好，
it's either it doesn't have enough pressure on it
要么是没有足够的压力，
or somebody's in the way.
要么是有手指挡住了。
So if you've got one notes like that
如果你有这样一个音符，
and you think you've got enough pressure on it,
你认为你已经有了足够的压力，
look and see if somebody is now sitting on that note,
看看有没有其他手指靠在那个音符上，
one of your other fingers
你的另一个手指，
and that will help your B7.
这会帮助你的 B7 。
Let's go through some exercises with these,
让我们用这些来做一些练习，
this would be your basic open chord exercises too.
这是你的基本开放和弦练习二。
Okay, start off with number one, starts on that G chord.
好的，从第一个开始，从那个 G 和弦开始。
Ready, six string chord,
准备，六根弦的和弦，
loose wrist, holding my pick strong,
松弛手腕，握紧拨片，
ready, go,
准备，开始，
a few beats to find that D7,
几拍时间来找到 D7 ，
only four string chord, be careful,
只有四根弦的和弦，小心一点，
if you need to look at your hand while you're playing,
如果你需要在弹奏的时候看你的手，
make sure you're getting the right number of strings,
确保你得到了正确的弦，
please do so.
请这样做。
Let's do number two,
让我们来做第二个，
C, we got some down and ups, having some eighth notes,
C ，我们有一些下上，有一些八分音符，
ready, go, down up, down up, down up, down up,
准备，开始，下上，下上，下上，下上，
D7, two three,
D7 ， 2 3 ，
or give you second to find it,
或者给你一些时间找到它，
good.
好的。
Number three, we have at B7,
第三个，我们有 B7 ，
three, jumping down to an Em,
3 ，跳到 Em ，
I gave you hard and then the easy one comes.
我给了你难的，然后简单的。
Great, so let's go to the last and third batch of chords.
好的，我们来看最后一批，第三批和弦。
Okay, now let's talk about the third set of chords,
好的，现在我们来讨论第三组和弦，
okay, we get it the first one we come across is a D,
好的，我们遇到的第一个和弦是 D ，
we've already done a Dm, D7,
我们已经做了 Dm D7 ，
now we are to the top of that chord family, the D,
现在我们到那个和弦家族的顶端， D ，
again all the D chords are four string chords,
再说一次，所有的 D 和弦都是四根弦的和弦，
we have open D,
我们有空弦 D ，
now you put your first finger on this third string A,
现在你把你的食指放在这第三弦 A 上，
curve your third finger over to catch this second string D
你的无名指放在第二弦 D 上，
and then your second finger,
然后你的第二根手指，
kind of squeezes up underneath there, on that first string to catch that #F,
挤在第一弦上，按住 F# ，
okay, let's do it together,
好的，让我们一起弹一次，
one more time,
再来一次，
all in one strum,
所有一次扫弦，
one more time, for good measure.
再来一次。
Next we come across is a C7,
下一个我们看的是 C7 ，
we've already done the C,
我们已经做了 C ，
remember what a C was like here,
记得 C 是什么样子的，
only thing different about a C7 is,
与 C7 的唯一不同之处是，
I put my pinky down on that third string on the third fret,
我把小拇指放在第三弦第三品上，
that's a C7.
这是 C7 。
Let me go slow, each individual note,
让我慢慢来，每一个音符，
now, if [] back a little bit too much with my wrist,
如果我的手腕往回收，
I may get some of the notes not coming out right,
可能会有一些音符出来不对，
bring that wrist down,
把手腕降低，
to where they can all come out properly.
到所有音符都能正确出来的地方。
Next one is an A,
下一个是 A ，
here's another five string chord,
这是另一个五根弦的和弦，
open A
空弦 A ，
and then there's the tricky thing about this one,
然后这个有个棘手的事情，
as I've got everybody's on that second fret,
因为每个手指都在第二品，
on the fourth, third and second string,
在第四弦、第三弦和第二弦上，
so how do we do that,
我们怎么做，
well, different guys do different ways,
不同的人做不同的方式，
here's what I'll give you two different ways,
这是我给你们的两种不同的方式，
here's the first way,
这是第一种方式，
use your second third and fourth finger
使用你的中指，无名指和小指，
and you just squeeze them all up underneath there together,
只需要把它们都挤在一起，
okay, now, sometimes they won't even fit
好的，有时它们甚至不适合，
and so you have to really kind of move your hand around
所以你必须移动你的手，
or you may have some of that sound like that,
或者你可能会有一些类似的声音，
squeeze them real in their type,
在它们的[类型]中挤压它们，
see if you can't open that up a little bit,
如果你不能开放一点，
now that's kind of the official way to play,
这是一种官方的方式，
sometimes in the heat of battle,
有时在激烈的[战斗]中，
you may take your first finger and bar this fourth, the third and the second string,
你可以使用食指，按住第四弦，第三弦和第二弦，
now a lot of guys do that,
现在很多人都这样做，
there's one problem with that
但有一个问题，
and it's on the first string,
那就是它在第一弦上，
there it is,
是这样的，
there's no way, unless you're you're double jointed,
这是没有办法的，除非你是双关节，
that you can get your first finger to bar all three of notes
你可以把你的食指横按在三个音符上，
and then invert to get off that last one,
然后翻过来，离开最后一个，
so it's good when you're on a rare back
所以，当你往回时，这是很好的，
and just kind of get the bottom four strings of it,
只是得到它的底部四根弦时，
but if you want to get the full chord,
但如果你想得到完整的和弦，
you really gotta work on getting these fingers to squeeze all up in together.
你需要努力让这些手指挤在一起。
Okay, A7, it's pretty easy,
好的， A7 ，它很简单，
we just take our A,
我们只需要使用 A ，
we move our third finger down and take our pinky out of the picture,
我们把无名指向下移动，把小拇指拿出来，
so we have open A,
所以我们有空弦 A ，
second finger on that fourth string,
中指在第四弦上，
open G,
空弦 G ，
make sure you can hear that open G,
确保你能听到空弦 G ，
make sure that second finger, make sure his rear end isn't sitting on that string
确保中指，确保他的后端没有靠在那根弦上，
and third finger squeezing up underneath there, that's #C,
无名指挤在这里， C# ，
and open.
然后空弦。
Very good, the last one we're going to cover is E,
很好，我们要介绍的最后一个是 E ，
all six strings on that E,
所有六根弦都在 E 上，
it's a E7, excuse me,
抱歉，它是 E7 ，
go ahead form it
继续形成它，
by making your E that we learned earlier,
通过修改我们学过的 E ，
remember that,
记得它吗，
now just take your third finger off,
现在把你的无名指拿开，
if we take our third finger off,
如果我们拿开无名指，
we're just left with our second and our first,
我们只剩下中指和食指，
and that's in E7.
这就是 E7 。
Of course getting easier, aren't they,
当然，现在变得更容易了，
probably pretty thankful about that by right about now.
现在可能很感激。
That's a E7,
这是 E7 ，
let's go through a couple of these exercises,
让我们来做几个练习，
basic open chord exercises number, basic chord exercises three,
基本开放和弦练习 3 ，
we're going to start with the first one,
我们将从第一个开始，
okay, starts on that D.
好的，从那个 D 开始。
Ready, play,
准备，弹奏，
four string chord,
四根弦的和弦，
give a second to find this A
给一点时间来找到 A ，
and squeeze all those fingers on that second fret,
然后把所有的手指都挤在第二品上，
go,
开始，
one more time to the D,
再来一次 D ，
ready play, back to A, two three four.
准备，弹奏，回到 A ， 2 3 4 ，
Very good.
非常好。
Okay, let's skip down a little bit,
好的，让我们跳到一点，
let's go down to, let's say number five,
让我们去第五个，
okay, that one starts on a G,
好的，这个从 G 开始，
now I'm starting to really get a little more complex
现在开始变得更复杂了，
with the chords, the quarter notes and the eighth notes of the chords,
有和弦，四分音符和八分音符，
okay, you have to pay attention to your rhythm a little bit,
你要注意你的节奏，
starts on a G,
从 G 开始，
we'll go nice and slow,
我们会慢一点，
ready, go,
准备，开始，
rest, rest,
休息，休息，
Em, rest,
Em ，休息，
C7, rest,
C7 ，休息，
D7, rest,
D7 ，休息，
on those down ups were accurate coming down
这些下上准确地落下来，
and we just had a couple of them coming up.
我们刚刚有几个下来了，
Let's do number, what was that number five, let's do number five again,
让我们再做一次第五个，
ready, go,
准备，开始，
rest rest,
休息，休息，
Em, rest,
Em ，休息，
C7, rest,
C7 ，休息，
D7, rest.
D7 ，休息。
Now you may have a problem with some of your chords,
现在，你的一些和弦可能会有问题，
it takes a little bit longer for you to actually form the chord
你需要更长的时间才能真正形成和弦，
and so you're kind of hesitating in between them,
所以你在它们之间有点犹豫，
you may do the first G
你可能会做第一个 G ，
and then it kind of takes a minute to get that Em,
然后需要一点时间才能得到 Em ，
the more you practice that, the quicker that transition will get,
你越多地练习，转换越快，
where you change those chords is important
在哪里转换和弦很重要，
and we'll talk about that in the next section.
我们将在下一节讨论这一点。
For our guitar tips section,
在我们的吉他技巧部分，
we're going to talk about two important concepts relating to chords,
我们将谈论两个与和弦相关的重要概念，
first of them is changing chords at the right time,
第一个是在正确的时间改变和弦，
this is very very important,
这一点非常非常重要，
a lot of times you're practicing these chord changes,
很多时候你都在练习这些和弦变化，
you're very worried about
你非常担心
getting making sure that all of these notes are coming out at the right time
确保所有这些音符都在正确的时间发出，
and that you're playing them enough times
以及你演奏了足够的次数，
and then it's time to play that next quarter
然后到了下一节演奏的时候，
and you've got to think about it there for a second.
你必须考虑一下这一点。
And then you gotta move on,
然后你必须继续前进，
okay, when you're actually playing a song,
当你真的在演奏一首歌曲的时候，
you gotta keep those chords in the right spots
你必须把和弦放在正确的位置，
or the song doesn't work.
否则这首歌就不会奏效。
So it's better for you to get through
所以对你来说，
and maybe chop off a couple of beats of that first chord
可能砍掉第一个和弦的几个节拍，
in order to land that second chord at the right time,
为了在正确的时间到达第二个和弦，
it's better to do that
这样做比较好，
than to catch every last drop of that first chord and miss the second chord,
抓住每个第一个和弦，错误第二个和弦，
I'd rather you cut off the first one,
我更希望你切断第一个和弦，
give yourself a little time
给自己一点时间，
to get what you need, where you need to get,
得到你需要的东西，
so that when it's time for that second chord,
这样当第二个和弦的时候，
when that split second comes by,
当那一瞬间到来的时候，
you're ready to land on that second chord.
你已经准备好登陆第二个和弦了。
Okay, changing chords at the proper time is very very important.
好的，在适当的时间改变和弦是非常非常重要的。
Next thing I want to talk about is an Em11,
接下来我想谈的是 Em11 ，
now you're probably going, what is an Em11,
现在你可能会想，什么是 Em11 ，
well, we'll learn what Em11 is in a few sessions,
我们将在几节课中学习什么是 Em11 ，
but for right now you need to know what this chord is
但现在你需要知道这个和弦是什么，
and never to do it,
永远不要这样做，
when you're going through a chord progression,
当你要进行和弦转换时，
let's say I'm going from a G, let's say to a C,
比方说，我从 G 到 C ，
so I'm gonna play four Gs, then I'm gonna do four Cs,
所以我要演奏四个 G ，然后我要演奏四个 C ，
now as you're just starting off in chords,
现在，因为你刚刚开始和弦，
you may be tempted to do this,
你可能会忍不住要这样做，
listen real carefully,
仔细听，
You hear how you have,
你们听到了，
right in between when I'm changing chords,
当我换和弦的时候，
I still have one strum left
我还有一次扫弦，
and I think, well, I can't make it and change chords at the right time,
我想我不能在正确的时间改变和弦，
so I just let that strum go
所以我把那个扫弦继续，
as my fingers are off the fret board over here
因为我的手指离开了这里的音板，
and you end up with Em11,
而你最终得到的是 Em11 ，
so you are not to play Em11 within between chords,
所以你不能在和弦之间演奏 Em11 ，
grab those chords as much as you can,
抓住你能抓住的和弦，
hang onto it, hang onto it
抓住它，
and then change really really quickly between the two,
然后在两个和弦之间非常迅速地转换，
so that you don't have that extra superfluous Em11 in the middle of everything,
这样你就不会有多余的 Em11 在中间了。
Okay, so if I'm speeding up a chord progression,
好的，所以如果我在加快和弦的进程，
maybe I'm doing something,
也许我在做一些东西，
which is a G, a C, a D7 and a G,
也就是 G C D7 G ，
well just to make sure you're changing chords,
好的，只是为了确保你改变和弦，
you're not throwing in that open strum,
你不会抛出那个开放的扫弦，
as you're changing chords,
当你改变和弦时，
which would sound something like this,
听起来像是这样，
real common guitar players do,
很多吉他演奏者都会这样做，
just because we're human and we like to be sloppy sometimes,
只是因为我们是人类，我们有时喜欢马虎，
so try and avoid doing that,
所以试着避免这样，
change those chords at exactly the proper time,
在正确的时间改变和弦，
so that when the chord changed, the song is going by,
这样当和弦改变时，歌曲继续，
that you're playing at the right chord at the right time.
在正确的和弦，正确的时间上演奏。
Okay, let's talk about your assignment for this session,
好的，让我们来谈谈这节课的作业，
your assignment for this session is,
这节课的作业是，
I want you to do all of the basic chord exercises in your book,
我想要你做书中所有的基本和弦练习，
which is basic exercises, one two and three.
也就是基本练习， 1 2 3 。
Okay, we're also going to,
好的，我们还会讲到，
there's basic chord songs in your book as, songs in your book as well,
书中还有基本和弦歌曲，
and I'd like for you to do those,
我想让你们做这些，
play through with the notes,
练习这些音符，
now that you've learned all your first position notes,
现在你已经学会了所有的第一把位音符，
remember notes a couple of sessions back,
记住几节课前的音符，
now we've got chords with them,
现在我们已经得到了和弦，
we're going to tie the two together.
我们要把这两个结合在一起。
Okay, so play the notes through one time,
好的，把音符弹一遍，
play the chords through one time.
把和弦弹一遍。
Okay, next thing is the workshop,
好的，下一件事是 workshop ，
I'll see you there.
我们在那里见。
Okay, welcome to the workshop time,
好的，欢迎来到 workshop 时间，
here we're gonna get some good workouts on the chords that we've learned,
这里我们将对学到的和弦进行一些很好的练习，
let's review the chords that we've covered so far.
让我们复习一下到目前为止已经学过的和弦。
Now I'm not going to say them,
现在我不打算说它们，
we aren't going to go through them, in the, in the order that we did before,
我们不是按照之前的顺序，
I'm going to group them into families.
我会把它们按[家族]分组。
Okay, so the first two we're going to cover is the C and the C7,
好的，所以我们要讲的前两个是 C 和 C7 ，
here's a C chord,
这是 C 和弦，
then for C7, all I have to do is put my pinky down,
然后 C7 ，我所要做的就是放下我的小拇指，
I want you to kind of start seeing how these all relate together,
我想让你看看这一切是如何联系在一起的，
let's play C, C7.
让我们弹奏 C ， C7 ，
Next is the D family,
接下来是 D 家族，
let's play D,
让我们弹奏 D ，
then Dm, got to switch your fingers around a little bit,
然后 Dm ，必须稍微交换一下手指，
D7,
D7 ，
let's do those one more time,
让我们再来一次，
D Dm D7.
D Dm D7 。
Now let's do the E family,
现在让我们来做 E 家族，
starts off with an E,
从 E 开始，
Em, take that first finger off,
Em ，把食指拿开，
put that first finger back on, take the third finger off, for E7.
把食指放回去，把无名指拿开，就是 E7 。
Do those again,
再做一次，
E Em E7.
E Em E7 。
Next, let's do the Gs,
接下来，让我们做 G ，
which would be G and G7,
也就是 G 和 G7 ，
start off with a G,
从 G 开始，
G7 now.
现在是 G7 。
One more time, G G7.
再来一次， G G7 。
Now let's do the A family,
现在让我们来做 A 家族，
A, member squeeze all those fingers in together,
A ，记得把所有手指挤在一起，
Am,
Am ，
A7, second and third finger.
A7 ，中指和无名指。
Let's do it all again,
让我们再来一次，
A Am A7.
A Am A7 。
And the lone one that's off by himself is a B7,
唯一一个自己出局的是 B7 ，
one more time, B7.
再来一次， B7 。
Okay, let's look at our basic open chord exercises number one,
好的，让我们来看看基本的开放和弦练习一，
we'll do exercise number one.
我们来做练习一。
Ready, play,
准备，弹奏，
G7, find it,
G7 ，找到它，
ready, go,
准备，开始，
repeated back to C,
重复回到 C ，
ready, play,
准备，弹奏，
G7,
G7 ，
ready, play.
准备，弹奏。
Let's move on the next one,
让我们到下一个，
number two, Am,
第二个， Am ，
ready, play,
准备，弹奏，
to the E,
切换到 E ，
repeated back to Am,
重复切换到 Am ，
ready, go,
准备，开始，
E two three four.
E 2 3 4 。
Number three, down and up,
第三个，下上，
so that C,
从 C 开始，
ready, go,
准备，开始，
Am two three four,
Am ， 2 3 4 ，
back to the C, two three four,
回到 C ，2 3 4 ，
Am, go,
Am ，继续，
three four, here we go, just stay right there on that Am,
3 4 ，我们继续，仍然在 Am ，
go,
弹奏，
next is a Dm, four string chord,
下一个是 Dm ，四个弦的和弦，
don't play those last fifth and sixth strings,
不要弹奏最后的第五弦和第六弦，
good, even strums,
好的，平稳的扫弦，
back to Am,
回到 Am ，
ready, go,
准备，开始，
nice, nice and loosen up that wrist,
很好，放松手腕，
Dm, go.
Dm ，弹奏。
Number five, down beats on the Dm,
第五个，下拍在 Dm 上，
ready, go,,
准备，开始，
G7, eighth notes,
G7 ，八分音符，
ready play,
准备，演奏，
back to Dm, ready go,
回到 Dm ，准备，开始，
G7.
G7 。
Last one, at the bottom of that page, number six,
最后一个，在页面底部，第六个，
starts on a C, go,
从 C 开始，弹奏，
quick change to Am, ready play,
快速切换到 Am ，准备，弹奏，
Dm, ready, play,
Dm ，准备，弹奏，
G7, ready, go.
G7 ，准备，开始。
One more time, back to C, go,
再来一次，回到 C ，开始，
find that Am, play,
找到 Am ，弹奏，
Dm, ready, go,
Dm ，准备，开始，
G7, ready play, two three four.
G7 ，准备，弹奏， 2 3 4 。
Okay, now let's do the basic chord exercises number two,
好的，现在让我们来做基本和弦练习二，
okay, starting on exercise number one,
好的，从练习一开始，
starts off with that G chord,
从 G 和弦开始，
we'll go a little bit faster this time,
这次我们会快一点，
ready play,
准备，弹奏，
D7, go,
D7 ，开始，
back to G, two three four,
回到 G ， 2 3 4 ，
D7.
D7 。
Number two, C, downs and ups, eighth notes,
第二个， C ，下上，八分音符，
make them nice and even,
使它们好而且均匀，
D7, just down beats,
D7 ，只有下拍，
oops, I gave you an extra beat there, sorry about that,
抱歉，我弹了一个额外的节拍，抱歉，
back to C, one more time just for me,
回到 C ，再来一次，
C, downs and ups and go,
C ，下上，开始，
D7, ready play,
D7 ，准备，弹奏，
now the B7, number three,
现在是 B7 ，第三个，
take a second, get your fingers in the right spots,
用一点时间，把你的手指放在正确的位置，
Em, two, that's the next one,
Em ， 2 ，这是下一个，
ready play,
准备，弹奏，
go ahead and repeat it, back to B7,
继续，重复它，回到 B7 ，
ready, go,
准备，开始，
Em, ready go.
Em ，准备，开始。
Very good, number four, Am,
很好，第四个， Am ，
here we go, pay attention to rhythm,
我们继续，注意节奏，
rest, rest and play Am again,
休息，休息，再次弹奏 Am ，
B7, go,
B7 ，开始，
rest, rest,
休息，休息，
go ahead, repeat it,
继续，重复，
back to Am, go,
回到 Am ，开始，
B7, go.
B7 ，开始。
Number five, go,
第五个，开始，
rest, rest, rest,
休息，休息，休息，
Em, rest, rest, rest, rest.
Bm ，休息，休息，休息，休息。
Now, I bet you, most of you missed that last measure there,
现在我打赌你们大多数人都错过了最后一节，
because I threw off one of the rest there,
因为丢了一个休息，
let's try one more time,
让我们再试一次，
make sure you get that,
确保你们已经注意到，
you've got to watch your counting on that one.
注意那里的计数。
Number five, starts on G, go,
第五个，从 G 开始，弹奏，
rest, rest, rest,
休息，休息，休息，
Em, rest rest,
Em ，休息，休息，
don't fall into the trap.
不要掉入陷阱中。
There you go, number six,
好的，第六个，
ready play,
准备，弹奏，
D7, play,
D7 ，弹奏，
Em, ready go,
Em ，准备，开始，
B7, go,
B7 ，开始，
repeat it back to G, play,
重复到 G ，弹奏，
D7, go,
D7 ，开始，
Em, ready go,
Em ，准备，开始，
B7, go, two three four.
B7 ，开始， 2 3 4 。
Okay, now let's look at the third set of guitar exercises,
好的，现在我们来看第三套吉他练习，
basic open chord exercises number three,
基本的开放和弦练习三，
okay, starts out on a D chord,
好的，从 D 和弦开始，
number one, ready play,
第一个，准备，开始，
get that A, squeeze all those fingers in there,
到 A ，把所有手指都挤进去，
repeated back to D,
重复回到 D ，
ready go,
准备，开始，
you're doing great,
你做得很好，
A, squeeze those fingers in there go.
A ，把手指放进去，开始。
Number two, C7, ready, play,
第二个， C7 ，准备，演奏，
A7 two three, five string chord,
A7 ， 2 3 ，无根弦的和弦，
back to C7, ready go,
回到 C7 ，准备，开始，
A7, ready go.
A7 ，准备，开始。
Doing great, number three,
做得很好，第三个，
Em, ready play,
Em ，准备，演奏，
A7, go,
A7 ，开始，
look at that rhythm, make sure you're getting all these eighth notes right,
看看节奏，确保你得到所有这些八分音符正确，
rest, B7,
休息， B7 ，
back to number three, go,
回到第三个，开始，
A7,
A7 ，
Em, ready, go,
Em ，准备，开始，
B7, rest.
B7 ，休息。
Number four, go, rest,
第四个，开始，休息，
D, here,
D ，这里，
look at these rhythms,
看着这些节奏，
E7, just take that third finger off.
E7 ，把无名指拿开。
Do it again.
再来一次。
Number five, ready, go,
第五个，准备，开始，
do it again, go,
再来一次，开始，
you're doing great.
你做得很好。
Number six,
第六个，
quickly change that Dm,
很快切换到 Dm ，
Am,
Am ，
G7.
G7 。
Do it again,
再来一次，
C, Dm, Am.
C ， Dm ， Am 。
Very good, we've gone through all those chord exercises,
很好，我们已经介绍了所有的和弦练习，
that's a lot of good practice for you,
这对你来说是很好的练习，
also there's more resources in the Jam Along CDs,
而且你的 Jam Along CD 中有更多的资源，
as well as there's more resources in your book as well,
你的书中也有更多资源，
let's move on to our songs.
让我们去看歌曲。
Okay, now let's look at some of our songs,
好的，现在让我们来看看我们的一些歌曲，
the first song to look at is Morning Has Broken,
第一首要看的歌曲是破晓，
okay, first thing we're gonna do is, is the notes,
好的，我们要做的第一件事是音符，
do the notes first,
先做音符，
okay, starts on it, starts on that C, on the fifth string,
好的，从第五弦的 C 开始，
we'll go through one time slow
我们慢的弹一次，
and we'll do one time fast,
我们快的弹一次，
since three four times, so three beats per measure,
因为是三四拍，所以每节有三拍，
here we go, starts on that C,
我们开始，从那个 C 开始，
ready, go,
准备，开始，
two three,
2 3 ，
two three.
2 3 。
Very good,
很好，
okay, now one more time with the notes
好的，音符再来一次，
a little bit faster this time.
这次快一点。
One, ready, go.
1 ，准备，开始。
Okay great,
好的，
now let's take a look at the chords,
现在让我们看一下和弦，
starts off with the C chord,
从 C 和弦开始，
okay, we're just gonna do a chord for each measure,
好的，我们只为每个小节做一个和弦，
okay, don't worry about doing strums just yet,
好的，现在不要担心扫弦，
if you want to strum along with each beat, that's fine,
如果你想跟着每个节拍扫弦，那很好，
we're going to do whole notes, that's fine too,
我们现在做全音符，也很好，
let's just do whole notes for now.
现在我们只做全音符。
Okay, starts out on a C chord,
好的，从 C 和弦开始，
now if there's a measure that's blank,
现在如果有一个小节是空白的，
you just keep repeating the chord of the previous measure,
你只要重复上一个小节的和弦，
that's how that works,
这就是工作原理，
it doesn't change until the actual chord change.
它不会改变，直到实际的和弦改变。
Here we go, starts on that C,
我们开始，从 C 开始，
I'll count you off,
我数一下，
one, ready, go,
1 ，准备，开始，
Dm,
Dm ，
now to a G,
现在到 G ，
to a Dm,
到 Dm ，
to a C,
到 C ，
here would be another C,
这里是另一个 C ，
Em,
Em ，
Am,
Am ，
D7,
D7 ，
G,
G ，
C,
C ，
Dm,
Dm ，
another Dm,
另一个 Dm ，
C,
C ，
Am,
Am ，
D,
D ，
G,
G ，
G7 here,
这里是 G7 ，
C,
C 。
Very good,
非常好，
okay, the last thing we're gonna do here is America The Beautiful,
好的，我们在这里最后要做的是 America The Beautiful ，
we're going to start off with our notes
我们将从音符开始，
and then we're gonna go to chords later,
然后我们将进入和弦，
so take a look at it,
所以看一下它，
let's do the notes first,
让我们先弹音符，
nice and slow,
优美而缓慢，
we have a pickup note on that D,
我们有一个拾音音符 D ，
ready play,
准备，弹奏，
#F,
F# ，
two three,
2 3 ，
here comes a #G, first finger,
这里有一个 G# ，食指，
#F here,
这里有 F# ，
two three,
2 3 ，
two three.
2 3 。
Very good, that one is a good workout on the dotted quarter note,
很好，这是一个四分音符加点的很好的锻炼，
we haven't really worked too much with a dotted quarter note,
我们还没有做太多的工作，四分音符加点，
gets a beat and a half
得到一拍加半拍，
and it's almost always followed by another eighth note,
它后面几乎总是有另一个八分音符，
is that would be,
就是这样，
dotted quarter, eighth quarter, okay.
加点的四分音符，八分音符，好的。
Let's do the chords this time, okay,
这次我们来弹奏和弦，好吗，
it's in four four time,
它是四四拍，
one, I'll catch you off, two,
1 ，我来数， 2 ，
ready go,
准备，开始，
two three four,
2 3 4 ，
one two three four,
1 2 3 4 ，
another D7,
另一个 D7 ，
now, G,
现在， G ，
stay on that G,
继续是 G ，
here comes some quick changes,
这里有一些快速的变化，
E7, A7, D7,
E7 ， A7 ， D7 ，
back to G,
回到 G ，
D and a quick D7,
D ，一个快速的 D7 ，
Am D7,
Am D7 ，
G,
G ，
C,
C ，
Am, D7,
Am ， D7 ，
G, two three four.
G 2 3 4 。
As you rehearse these more,
随着你排练这些更多，
you can start adding more beats into it,
你可以开始加入更多的节拍，
maybe chords with every beat
也许每一个节拍都能和弦，
rather than just doing whole note like we did there,
而不是像我们在那里全音符，
but we've got to start somewhere,
但我们必须从某个地方开始，
so we start off with whole notes.
所以我们从全音符开始。
So, thanks, and we will see you next time.
所以，谢谢，我们下次再见。